<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cinema</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="favorite">Favorite</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="sort">Sort Movies</string>


    <array name="movie_title">

        <item>Kumathon</item>
        <item>Exorcist:Believer</item>
        <item>Dr.Cheon And The Lost Talisman</item>
        <item>Past Lives</item>
        <item>The Creator</item>
        <item>EXPEND4BLES</item>
        <item>The Nun 2</item>
        <item>Batman Begins</item>


        <item>Hunger Games</item>
        <item>It Lives Inside</item>
        <item>Day Dreamers</item>
        <item>The Dark Knight</item>
        <item>The Marvels</item>
        <item>Dune 2</item>
        <item>Five nights at Freddy\'s</item>
        <item>Cobweb</item>
    </array>

    <array name="movie_trailer">

        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XC3ftnZ1WYk</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rSGeC880CYw</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6NuQArwFhlA</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kA244xewjcI</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ex3C1-5Dhb8</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DhlaBO-SwVE</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QF-oyCwaArU</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=neY2xVmOfUM</item>


        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RDE6Uz73A7g</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FrPYOf5RmYI</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L3t9jW4eRAs</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EXeTwQWrcwY</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wS_qbDztgVY</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_YUzQa_1RCE</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z_T0o5uNrlY</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yusx3Gma9jI</item>
    </array>

    <array name="movie_release_date">
        <item>10/06/2023</item>
        <item>10/06/2023</item>
        <item>10/06/2023</item>
        <item>09/29/2023</item>
        <item>09/29/2023</item>
        <item>09/22/2023</item>
        <item>09/08/2023</item>
        <item>09/27/2023</item>

        <item>11/17/2023</item>
        <item>10/20/2023</item>
        <item>12/08/2023</item>
        <item>10/18/2023</item>
        <item>11/10/2023</item>
        <item>11/03/2023</item>
        <item>10/27/2023</item>
        <item>10/13/2023</item>
    </array>
    <array name="movie_ratings">
        <item>4.5</item>
        <item>3.5</item>
        <item>4.2</item>
        <item>4.8</item>
        <item>5.0</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>4.1</item>
        <item>4.7</item>
        <item>4.6</item>
        <item>3.9</item>
        <item>4.3</item>
        <item>4.4</item>
        <item>4.0</item>
        <item>3.7</item>
        <item>4.9</item>
        <item>3.6</item>
    </array>

    <array name="movie_description">

        <item>The story happened when \" Ging \" took his son on vacation at the house in the middle
            of the forest. There was a strange man who broke into the house and kidnapped her son.
            Ging went to report the police, so she knew that the man named \" In \" was an
            undertaker at the temple. But the undertaker said he didn \' t break into the house.
            Ging had to find evidence to blame the undertaker but couldn \' t catch it. And Ging
            still had to face the secret story that happened in the house, so she looked for \" Hike
            \" in the forest to ask for help. But returned to the forest and happened to see \" In
            \" doing a ritual to take the child \' s body to make a child. In chased the branch
            until she lost consciousness. When \" Nop \" came to the Ging \' s girlfriend came to
            the house with \" Pam \", the nurse who helped him. She found that the branch was
            unconscious like a madman.
        </item>
        <item>When single father Victor Fielding\'s daughter, Angela, and her friend Katherine, show
            signs of demonic possession, it unleashes a chain of events that forces him to confront
            the nadir of evil. Terrified and desperate, he seeks out Chris MacNeil, the only person
            alive who\'s witnessed anything like it before.
        </item>
        <item>The story of a fake exorcist, Dr. Cheon, who is commissioned for the case of a girl
            who is strongly possessed.
        </item>
        <item>In Korea, Na Young, a girl and Hae Sung, a boy are school mates and good friends. They
            often walk back home together after school. Na Young moves to Canada and then to New
            York with her parents. Hae Sung continues living in Korea, does his engineering course,
            goes through a short spell of military service and then takes up a job. Both keep in
            touch periodically through video chats where they talk of their past and general stuff.
            Meanwhile in New York, Na has changed her name to Nora, made a name as a playwright and
            is happily married to Arthur, an American. Hae is keen to meet Nora and visits her in
            New York where he spends some time with her and Arthur. What has the future in store for
            Nora and Hae in their relationship?
        </item>
        <item>Amid a future war between the human race and the forces of artificial intelligence,
            Joshua, a hardened ex-special forces agent grieving the disappearance of his wife, is
            recruited to hunt down and kill the Creator, the elusive architect of advanced AI who
            has developed a mysterious weapon with the power to end the war-and mankind itself.
        </item>
        <item>A new generation of stars join the world\'s top action stars for an adrenaline-fueled
            adventure in Expend4bles. Reuniting as the team of elite mercenaries, Jason Statham,
            Dolph Lundgren, Randy Couture, and Sylvester Stallone are joined for the first time by
            Curtis \"50 Cent\" Jackson, Megan Fox, Tony Jaa, Iko Uwais, Jacob Scipio, Levy Tran, and
            Andy Garcia. Armed with every weapon they can get their hands on and the skills to use
            them, The Expendables are the world\'s last line of defense and the team that gets
            called when all other options are off the table. But new team members with new styles
            and tactics are going to give \"new blood\" a whole new meaning.
        </item>
        <item>A follow-up to the enigmatic gothic horror about a strong evil that haunts and causes
            supernatural harm to everybody it comes into contact with. After the events of the first
            film, the said powerful evil now begins to spread in 1956 throughout a town in France as
            word gets out that a priest has been violently murdered. A finished contemplative in her
            novitiate, Sister Irene, begins to investigate the murder, only to find a demon behind
            it -- the same evil that terrorized her in the original film as a nun -- Valak, whom she
            once again soon comes to encounter.
        </item>
        <item>When his parents are killed, billionaire playboy Bruce Wayne relocates to Asia, where
            he is mentored by Henri Ducard and Ra\'s Al Ghul in how to fight evil. When learning
            about the plan to wipe out evil in Gotham City by Ducard, Bruce prevents this plan from
            getting any further and heads back to his home. Back in his original surroundings, Bruce
            adopts the image of a bat to strike fear into the criminals and the corrupt as the icon
            known as \"Batman"\. But it doesn't stay quiet for long.
        </item>

        <item>Coriolanus Snow at age 18, years before he would become the tyrannical President of
            Panem. Young Coriolanus is handsome and charming, and though the Snow family has fallen
            on hard times, he sees a chance for a change in his fortunes when he is chosen to be a
            mentor for the Tenth Hunger Games. Only to have his elation dashed when he is assigned
            to mentor the girl tribute from impoverished District 12.
        </item>
        <item>Sam, an Indian-American teen, lives in an idyllic suburb with her conservative mother
            and her assimilated father. Sam\'s cultural insecurities grow due to her estranged
            friend, Tamira, who mysteriously carries around an empty mason jar all the time. In a
            moment of anger, Sam breaks Tamira\'s jar and unleashes an ancient Indian demonic force
            that kidnaps Tamira. Sam searches for Tamira, following the trail of a young man who
            performed a deadly ritual, until the demonic entity starts targeting her, murdering her
            boyfriend and shattering her reality with terrifying visions. Sam must band together
            with her parents and a sympathetic teacher to save Tamira and put an end to the terror
            of the demon.
        </item>
        <item>For hundreds of years, vampires have lived in peace and harmony among humans, but this
            way of life is interrupted when a human girl discovers the true identity of two vampire
            brothers. One brother\’s thirst for blood vows to kill the girl in order to protect his
            kind, while the other races against time to protect her. In the end, only one will
            survive.
        </item>
        <item>Set within a year after the events of Batman Begins (2005), Batman, Lieutenant James
            Gordon, and new District Attorney Harvey Dent successfully begin to round up the
            criminals that plague Gotham City, until a mysterious and sadistic criminal mastermind
            known only as \"The Joker"\ appears in Gotham, creating a new wave of chaos. Batman\'s
            struggle against The Joker becomes deeply personal, forcing him to \"confront everything
            he believes"\ and improve his technology to stop him. A love triangle develops between
            Bruce Wayne, Dent, and Rachel Dawes.
        </item>
        <item>Carol Danvers AKA Captain Marvel has reclaimed her identity from the tyrannical Kree
            and taken revenge on the Supreme Intelligence. But unintended consequences see Carol
            shouldering the burden of a destabilized universe. When her duties send her to an
            anomalous wormhole linked to a Kree revolutionary, her powers become entangled with that
            of Jersey City super-fan Kamala Khan, aka Ms. Marvel, and Carol\'s estranged niece, now
            S.A.B.E.R. astronaut Captain Monica Rambeau.
        </item>
        <item>A boy becomes the Messiah of nomads on a desert planet that has giant worms that
            protect a commodity called Spice. Spice changes people into travelers, mystics and
            madmen. What price will he pay to become the new ruler of their universe?
        </item>
        <item>A troubled security guard begins working at Freddy Fazbear\'s Pizza. During his first
            night on the job, he realizes that the night shift won\'t be so easy to get through.
            Pretty soon he will unveil what actually happened at Freddy\'s.
        </item>
        <item>\"In 1970s Korea, when both art and dreams are censored, a film director dreams of a
            masterpiece. After his successful debut, Director KIM endures scathing attacks from
            critics who call him a specialist in trashy dramas. After finishing his latest feature
            \u2018Cobweb\u2019, he has vivid dreams over several days of an alternative ending to
            the film. Sensing that if he can just shoot those scenes as he envisioned them, a
            masterpiece will surely emerge, he tries to arrange just two days of additional
            shooting. However, the rewritten script fails to pass censorship, and his actors
            can\u2019t make sense of the new ending. Between the tangled schedule, the opposition of
            the producer, and the collision between these fantastic scenes dancing before his eyes
            and the harsh conditions of reality, Director KIM feels he is about to go insane, but he
            pushes on regardless\u2026 \u201CIf I can just change the ending, a masterpiece will
            emerge. All I need is two days!\u201D\"
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="movie_booking">

        <item>https://www.cgv.vn/en/kumarn.html</item>
        <item>https://www.cgv.vn/default/exorcist-believer.html</item>
        <item>https://www.cgv.vn/default/dr-cheon.html</item>
        <item>https://www.cgv.vn/default/past-lives.html</item>
        <item>https://www.cgv.vn/default/the-creator.html</item>
        <item>https://www.cgv.vn/default/expend4bles.html</item>
        <item>https://www.cgv.vn/default/the-nun-2.html</item>
        <item>https://www.cgv.vn/default/batman-begins.html</item>


        <item>https://www.cgv.vn/default/the-hunger-games.html</item>
        <item>https://www.cgv.vn/default/it-lives-inside.html</item>
        <item>https://www.cgv.vn/default/nguoi-mat-troi.html</item>
        <item>https://www.cgv.vn/default/the-dark-knight.html</item>
        <item>https://www.cgv.vn/default/the-marvels.html</item>
        <item>https://www.cgv.vn/default/dune-2.html</item>
        <item>https://www.cgv.vn/default/5-dem-kinh-hoang.html</item>
        <item>https://www.cgv.vn/default/cobweb.html</item>
    </array>

    <integer-array name="movie_duration">

        <item>88</item>
        <item>111</item>
        <item>98</item>
        <item>106</item>
        <item>133</item>
        <item>103</item>
        <item>110</item>
        <item>140</item>


        <item>165</item>
        <item>98</item>
        <item>100</item>
        <item>152</item>
        <item>105</item>
        <item>150</item>
        <item>110</item>
        <item>132</item>
    </integer-array>

    <array name="movie_category">

        <item>Horror</item>
        <item>Horror</item>
        <item>Comedy</item>
        <item>Romance</item>
        <item>Sci-fi</item>
        <item>Action</item>
        <item>Horror</item>
        <item>Action</item>


        <item>Action</item>
        <item>Horror</item>
        <item>Action</item>
        <item>Action</item>
        <item>Action</item>
        <item>Adventure</item>
        <item>Horror</item>
        <item>Comedy</item>
    </array>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


</resources>